<resources>
    <string name="app_name">2ndPractical</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_repository">Reader Activity</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title">Title</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="reader">Reader</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="author">Author</string>
    <string name="publisher">Publisher</string>

    <string name="Place1Title">Rūjiena</string>
        <string name="Place1Descr">
            Rūjiena is a town in Valmiera Municipality, in the Vidzeme region of Latvia. As of 2017 its population was 3,007.
        </string>
        <string name="Place1LngLat">57.89384262908556, 25.3386254405581</string>
    <string name="Place2Title"> Mazsalaca </string>
        <string name="Place2Descr">
            Mazsalaca is a town in Valmiera Municipality in the Vidzeme region of Latvia. It has 1269 inhabitants.
        </string>
        <string name="Place2LngLat">57.86069654002818, 25.053938581073744</string>
    <string name="Place3Title">Salacgrīva</string>
        <string name="Place3Descr">
            Salacgrīva is a town in Salacgrīva Municipality in the Vidzeme region of Latvia.
            The centre of the area surrounding Salacgrīva is the mouth of Salaca River,
            and the town\s name literally means \Mouth of Salaca\ in Latvian.
        </string>
        <string name="Place3LngLat">57.770367321244386, 24.36052977941047</string>
    <string name="Place4Title">Limbaži</string>
        <string name="Place4Descr">
            Limbaži is a town in the Vidzeme region of northern Latvia. Limbaži is located 90 km northeast
            of the capital Riga. The population is 6888 people. During the Middle Ages, as part of Livonia,
            Limbaži was a fortified town with stone walls, second in importance only to Riga.
        </string>
        <string name="Place4LngLat">57.51504395380812, 24.720529305795008</string>
    <string name="Place5Title">Valmiera</string>
        <string name="Place5Descr">
            Valmiera is the largest city of the historical Vidzeme region, Latvia, with a total area of 19.35
            square kilometres. As of 2002, Valmiera had a population of 27,323, and in 2020 – 24 879.
            It is the seat of Valmiera Municipality.
        </string>
        <string name="Place5LngLat">57.531598337692515, 25.423781119233627</string>
    <string name="Place6Title">Smiltene</string>
        <string name="Place6Descr">
            Smiltene is a town in the Vidzeme region in northern Latvia, 132 km northeast of the capital
            Riga, and the administrative centre of Smiltene Municipality. It has a population of 5,536.
        </string>
        <string name="Place6LngLat">57.42327954381972, 25.90154064611188</string>
    <string name="Place8Title">Cēsis</string>
        <string name="Place8Descr">
            Cēsis is a town in northeastern Latvia, known for its medieval castle. First built in the
            13th century and rebuilt many times since, Cēsis Castle features wall paintings,
            dungeons and towers with views. Its Castle Park includes an old brewery, a cemetery and
            the Transfiguration of Christ Orthodox Church. Also on castle grounds, the 18th-century
            Castle Manor House is home to the Cēsis History and Art Museum.
        </string>
        <string name="Place8LngLat">57.30955796296143, 25.263889457035255</string>
    <string name="Place9Title">Saulkrasti</string>
        <string name="Place9Descr">
            Saulkrasti is a town in Latvia on the east coast of the Gulf of Riga and the capital of
            the Saulkrasti municipality. Made up of a number of historic fishing settlements, the
            town stretches for some 17 km from the Inčupe river in the south to the village of Skulte in the north.
        </string>
        <string name="Place9LngLat">57.26783917449651, 24.410921463443614</string>
    <string name="Place10Title">Sigulda</string>
        <string name="Place10Descr">
            Sigulda is a town in the Vidzeme Region of Latvia, 53 kilometres from the capital city Riga.
        </string>
        <string name="Place10LngLat">57.149830418833915, 24.86032460675555</string>
    <string name="Place11Title">Ādaži</string>
        <string name="Place11Descr">
            Ādaži is a town in Pierīga, on the left bank of the Gauja river. Town is administrative
            center of Ādaži Municipality. It is located by the highway A1, 21.6 km from the center
            of Riga. Ādaži has administrative offices, schools, Kindergarten Strautins, several shops and service companies.
        </string>
        <string name="Place11LngLat">57.06651259931646, 24.343401944734293</string>
    <string name="Place12Title">Rīga</string>
        <string name="Place12Descr">
            Riga, Latvia’s capital, is set on the Baltic Sea at the mouth of the River Daugava.
            Its considered a cultural center and is home to many museums and concert halls.
            The city is also known for its wooden buildings, art nouveau architecture and medieval
            Old Town. The pedestrian-only Old Town has many shops and restaurants and is home to busy
            Livu Square, with bars and nightclubs.
        </string>
        <string name="Place12LngLat">56.9492525748426, 24.1022536572613</string>
    <string name="Place13Title">Ērgļi</string>
        <string name="Place13Descr">
            Ērgļi is a small town in Ērgļi Parish, Madona Municipality in the Vidzeme region of
            Latvia on the banks of the Ogre river. It serves as the administrative center for
            Ērgļi Parish. Ērgļi had 2,769 residents as of 2017.
        </string>
        <string name="Place13LngLat">56.899063405265565, 25.63980184449221</string>
    <string name="Place14Title">Gulbene</string>
        <string name="Place14Descr">
            Gulbene is a town in northeastern Latvia. It is an administrative center of Gulbene
            Municipality. The area of this region is 11.898 km², with a population of 29,797
            inhabitants.
        </string>
        <string name="Place14LngLat">57.17148343630817, 26.751777508960682</string>
    <string name="Place15Title">Alūksne</string>
        <string name="Place15Descr">
            Alūksne is a town on the shores of Lake Alūksne in northeastern Latvia near
            the borders with Estonia and Russia. It is the seat of Alūksne municipality.
            Alūksne is the highest elevated Latvian city, located in East Vidzeme Upland
            at 217 m above sea level.
        </string>
        <string name="Place15LngLat">57.42073042352515, 27.051321538919982</string>
</resources>